pivps.com 2017-05-13

# Privacy Policy | Cheap Windows VPS & Linux VPS Services

### Latest news and updates from PiVPS

[PiVPS](http://www.pivps.com/) (PiVPS) prides itself on protecting your privacy and developing technology to give you the most powerful and safe online experience possible. This Privacy Policy applies to PiVPS and governs data collection and usage. PiVPS is governed by the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act. By using the PiVPS website, you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Policy.

PiVPS has developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its firm commitment to privacy and security.

### How PiVPS Collects Your Personal Information

PiVPS collects personally identifiable information in a variety of ways. Any information you enter on our websites or online forms for products and services, or that you volunteer in any other way, will be collected. The data collected may include your:

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Home and/or work address and/or telephone number
  * Credit card and other billing information

Certain information about your computer hardware and software may also be automatically collected by PiVPS. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times, and referring website addresses. This information is used by PiVPS for the operation of the service, to maintain the quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the PiVPS website and its services.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through PiVPS public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Note: PiVPS does not read any of your private online communications.

### How PiVPS Uses & Discloses Your Personal Information

**(i) Provision of Services**

PiVPS collects and uses your personal information to operate the PiVPS website and to deliver the services you have requested. PiVPS also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from PiVPS and its affiliates.

**(ii) Surveys**

PiVPS may also contact you via surveys to conduct market research and collect opinions about current services or new services that may be offered.

**(iii) Analysis**

PiVPS keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within PiVPS in order to determine which PiVPS services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within PiVPS to customers whose behaviour indicates they are interested in a particular subject area.

**(iv) Third-Party Services**

PiVPS offers some products and services in conjunction with or through trusted partners, sponsors, and affiliates (“Third-Party Services”). If you provide your personal information in conjunction with any Third-Party Services, you will be advised at the point of collection who is collecting the information and whose privacy policy applies. If there is any doubt, please contact PiVPS to clarify (see contact information below). If this Privacy Policy applies to such personal information, then PiVPS may be required to disclose your information to our trusted partner, sponsor, or affiliate in order to provide the Third-Party Services. If the privacy policy of our trusted partner, sponsor, or affiliate applies, PiVPS will make all reasonable efforts to ensure the third-party privacy policy is properly in place and complied with. However, it is your responsibility to satisfy yourself with such privacy policies, as Third-Party Services have separate and independent privacy policies. PiVPS accepts no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of Third-Party Services. Nonetheless, PiVPS welcomes comments and feedback relating to Third-Party Services.

**(v) Links**

You may be able to access other websites that have links on PiVPS websites, where you can purchase products and services or register to receive materials or new product updates. In many of these cases, you will be asked to provide personal information such as your name, email address, or other contact information, or credit/billing information. If you complete an order or provide personal information to a website or service that is not provided by PiVPS, PiVPS has no control over the third party’s use of any personal information. PiVPS therefore has no responsibility or liability for the manner in which the organizations that operate such linked websites may collect, use, disclose, secure, or otherwise deal with your personal information. PiVPS provides these links to other websites as a convenience to you. Please exercise care when visiting linked websites, which will have separate and independent privacy policies.

**(vi) Legal Disclosure**

PiVPS collects, uses, and discloses your personal information as described above. However, PiVPS, its affiliates, trusted partners, and sponsors, may disclose your personal information, including your use of the services or websites accessible through the services, for any reason, in its sole discretion to comply with Canadian, U.S., or other laws, regulations, or governmental or legal requests or demands for such information, and act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of PiVPS or the public.

### Domain Registration

In certain jurisdictions or pursuant to the rules of the Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers (“ICANN”) or certain registries, domain name registration information legally has to be available to the public. Where domain name registration information is available to the public, anyone can access it through “WHOIS” searches. The WHOIS database is a publicly accessible database that lists the domain name and contact information of the registrant and administrative and technical contacts for the domain name, the name server(s), and the domain name’s creation and expiration date. The domain name registration information you provide may be hosted by us and provided to the public. At times, users of PiVPS may receive solicitations that result from searches of the publicly available WHOIS database conducted by other companies or individuals. However, the solicitation and/or SPAM you receive does not in any way come from PiVPS and PiVPS does not control the use of WHOIS information by third parties. Further, pursuant to ICANN rules, PiVPS is required to make WHOIS data available to a third party that enters into a bulk access agreement. ICANN allows individuals to opt-out (using the account management panel, domain management console, or similar service) of their WHOIS information being made available to third parties through bulk access; however, companies, businesses, and other organizations do not have the option to choose not to have their information made available to such a third party under a bulk access agreement. PiVPS may also deposit your domain name registration information with a third-party escrow provider to comply with ICANN requirements.

### International Transfer of Data

If you visit PiVPS or its websites from a country other than the country in which our servers are located, your communications with PiVPS may result in the transfer of information across international borders. By using PiVPS services and communicating with PiVPS, you consent to such transfers.

### Use of Cookies

PiVPS uses “cookies” to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize PiVPS pages, or register with a PiVPS site or service, a cookie helps PiVPS recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same PiVPS website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the PiVPS features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the PiVPS websites or services you visit.

### Security of Your Personal Information

PiVPS secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. PiVPS secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. PiVPS maintains reasonable administrative, technical, and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification, and disclosure of personal information in its control and custody. However, no data transmission over the Internet or wireless network can be guaranteed 100% secure. Therefore, while PiVPS strives to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that (i) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond the control of PiVPS; (ii) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and PiVPS through the website cannot be guaranteed; and (iii) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party, despite best efforts.

### Access and Modifying Your Information

You have the right to access, update, and correct any inaccuracies in your personal information that we control, subject to certain exceptions set out in this Privacy Policy. You may request access, update, and correct any inaccuracies in your personal information by contacting us by email (info@PiVPS.com) or regular mail (PiVPS, 115 George St., Suite 511, Oakville, Ontario, Canada L6J 0A2). We may request certain personal information in order to verify your identity.

To ensure you receive the information you need and your privacy is protected, please be sure to regularly update your contact and billing information. You can update all account-related information through the PiVPS website.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

PiVPS will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback. PiVPS encourages you to provide feedback and to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed of how PiVPS is protecting your information.

### Sale of Business

We wish to clarify and confirm that PiVPS may transfer your personal information as an asset in connection with a merger or sale (including bankruptcy or insolvency proceedings) involving all or part of PiVPS, whether by corporate reorganization, share sale, asset sale, or other change of control. PiVPS may share your personal information with other entities owned by PiVPS or that own PiVPS.
